(Penny:)How are we supposed to set up machines
and conveyor belts in my apartment?
(Sheldon:)You're thinking of
the moving assembly line.
(Sheldon:)An understandable,
but not excusable, mistake. Now...
(Sheldon:)...the moving assembly line, that was
introduced by Henry Ford in 1908.
(Sheldon:)That innovation is what made possible
our modern consumer culture...
...by enabling a low unit cost
for manufactured goods.
(Sheldon:)I guess that isn't one of the topics
discussed on your Radiohead.
We're gonna miss the coming attractions.
[GROANS]
(Raj:)What's the matter?
(Howard:)I think I bruised a testicle
capturing that last pawn.
[PENNY & SHELDON SINGING
"BLOW THE MAN DOWN"]
PENNY & SHELDON [SINGING]:
Give me some time to blow the man down
I'm a deep-water sailor
Just come from Hong Kong
BOTH:
To me way, hey, blow the man down
If you give me some whiskey
I'll sing you a song